Oh, dear heavens, what cruel fate has befallen us?
She clasped her hands to her chest, her voice trembling with disbelief.
To find you thus in such a manner is beyond my comprehension.
How could I have ventured away, thinking the world was as it should be, only to return to this ghastly sight?
You were my anchor, my beloved, and now I stand here, utterly lost.
What will become of me?
Our hopes and dreams lie shattered upon the floor, and the very air feels heavy with sorrow.
I beseech you, do not leave me in this wretched state.
Life without you is an unthinkable torment, one I cannot bear to contemplate.
I implore the heavens above to restore you, for my heart can scarcely endure this anguish.
Subs by www.zeoranger.co.uk